Guide to the Paul Brockman papers, 1971-1976
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Paul Brockman papers
1971-1976
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Paul R. Brockman
C0087
4.5 linear feet (9 boxes)
This collection documents Paul Brockman's service as a councilman on the Falls Church City Council in Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Paul Brockman in 1978.
Biographical Information
Paul R. Brockman served on the Falls Church City Council in Virginia from 1971 until 1976. Falls Church was incorporated as a town in 1875 and as an independent city in 1948 and has operated under a Council-Manager form of government since 1950.
Scope and Content
This collection documents Paul Brockman's service as a councilman on the Falls Church City Council in Virginia. The collection is in one series, arranged alphabetically by subject. The material includes information on various city programs, including the Metro system, licensures and general budget.
Arrangement
This collection is organized by subject and date.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collection and Archives holds many other collections on Northern Virginia politics and government.
Index Terms
Persons:
Brockman, Paul R.
Corporate Names:
Falls Church (Va.). City Councl.
Geographical Names:
Falls Church (Va.)--Politics and government.
Subjects:
City planning--Virginia--Falls Church.
Contents List
- Paul Brockman papers
  - Air Pollution, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Animal and Fowl, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Architectural Advisory Board (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bicycles, Minibikes on Sidewalks, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Zoning Appeals I, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Zoning Appeals II, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bond Issue, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Budget and Transit Studies I, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Budget and Transit Studies II, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Budget I, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Budget II, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Budget III, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Buildings - Code Variances, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Business License Taxes, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Business Practices - Home Improvement, Business License and Bond, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Capital Improvements - Streets, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Charter Revisions, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Child Care Services, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - City Financing, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - City Personnel Matters, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - City Planning, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cloverdale Property, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Crossroads Project I, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Crossroads Project II, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Consumer Protection, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Crossroads I, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Crossroads II, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Employment Centers - Department of Defense Facilities (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Erosion and Siltation Control, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Exceptional Children, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fair Share-Housing Formula, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Financial Controls, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fire Arms and Gun Controls, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Franchises, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Goals, Objectives and Standards, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hechinger Building I, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hechinger Building II, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hechinger- Massive Buildings, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Housing I, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Housing II, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Interstate 66, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Landscaping - Escrow Deposits, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Law Enforcement Advisory Commission, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Massage Parlor Regulation, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mental Health, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Metro Bus-Rail Fares I, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Metro Bus-Rail Fares II, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Metro and It's Impact, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Metro Meeting Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Metro - West Falls Church Station, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Metro - "The 2000 Plan", 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Noise Control, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Notes and Rough Drafts, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Outdoor Lighting, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Planning Commission, 1971, 1976-1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Planning Departments - Responsibilities, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Police Pensions - City, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Quotas - Fair Shows, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Restaurants - Free Standing, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Robs Ketch - Planned Unit Development, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Salem Church, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - School Facilities, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Search Warrants - Inspections, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Senior Citizens, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sewer Rates, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Signs, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Streets and Sidewalks, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Surface Runoff, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Task Force Materials, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Tax Relief for the Elderly, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Taxicabs, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Transfers of Funds, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Trees and Shrubs, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tripps Run, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Trucks - Parking in Residential Areas, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Utilities, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Water Systems and Rates, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Zoning, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)